New York State plans to shut off the thundering waters of Niagara Falls again, at
least the American side of falls.
least the American side of the falls.
New York State plans to shut off the thundering waters of Niagara Falls again, at
This once -in -a -lifetime event actually may take place twice in some folks'
lives. This once -in -a -lifetime event actually may take place twice in some folks'
lives. The New York State Parks System wants to turn off the falls on the American
side sometime in the next two to three years to replace two 115 -year -old stone
bridges that allow pedestrians, park vehicles, and utilities access to Goat Island.
The New York State Parks System wants to turn off the falls on the American side
sometime in the next two to three years to replace two 115 -year -old stone bridges
that allow pedestrians, park vehicles, and utilities access to Goat Island.
The New York State Parks System wants to turn off the falls on the American side
sometime in the next two to three years to replace two 115 -year -old stone bridges
that allow pedestrians, park vehicles, and utilities access to Goat Island.
The American side of the falls was shut off in 1969 to study the buildup of rock at
the base of the falls.
When that happened, people came from all over the world to see the falls turned off.
People are curious by nature.
They want to see what's underneath.
When that happened, people came from all over